I'm starving.
Let's grab a bite first.
What do you want, Chinatsu?
Buttered potatoes!
Sounds good.
Takoyaki sounds good too.
Whoa! Look who we have here!
Aren't they first-years?
I wonder if they're on a date.
I wish I came in a yukata!
Her hairstyle's so cute too!
Aw, to be young again.
BLUE BOX
Morning arrives with my emotions a complete mess
A sharp emotion tugging deep within my chest
This love I feel inside, all this love I feel for you
It's too much, and it's so hard to bear
I get dizzy from how close we are, yet it feels so far
The highs and lows freeze and thaw my soul
The weight on my heart grows with my feelings
I just can't bear to let them go
I'm definitely gonna land a smash!
And I'm sinking my shots for sure!
Even as my heart aches, I still want to scream out to you
I'm captivated by you in spring
I'm entranced by your beauty in summer's glow
The world changes around us
but my heart stays blue, as my feelings only grow
I'm mesmerized as the snowflakes fall around you
in the autumn sky, and it suits you perfectly
My love thrives, even in this hectic world
without a spare second to look away
I'm in love with the season that is you
BLUE BOX
Episode 12: Girls...
She's so quiet.
I don't think she's ever been
quiet for this long.
I'm gonna get some yakisoba!
We can go together!
I'm so nervous.
I wanted to come with just him..
but Kyo had to suddenly drop out.
Just the two of us?
That's cool
with me.
Did eating that candy apple
rub off my lipstick?
My bangs aren't mussed up, right?
My obi's not twisted, right?
YAKISOBA
500 YEN
I want him to really notice me.
Step right up!
I worked hard on this getup...
If I can...
If I can... just make
him think I look cute.
But I'm also worried that I look weird.
I've never dressed like this before...
so a part of me's embarrassed.
I want him to look at me,
but I also not look at me.
Let's set it up here.
Watch out for pebbles.
Thanks.
We still have about 10 minutes.
Yeah.
You need anything to drink?
I'm fine.
Here I thought everything was normal...
but something's definitely up with her.
She's being targeted.
I guess she already got bitten.
Wanna use this?
Yeah.
Thanks.
It must itch.
You'll get it on your yukata like that.
Give it here.
It's a lil more to the left.
Oh, damn.
This is more awkward than I thought.
A lil bit of hair came loose.
Did you do your hair yourself?
Yeah, I did.
Why?
I'm just surprised you have
such a delicate touch.
Are you making fun of me?
Not at all.
I'm honestly impressed.
Now it really sounds like
you're messing with me.
Did some of it come loose?!
See, you really are trying to rile me up.
Don't twist my words.
It's not easy to do,
but you worked hard at it.
I think it looks cute,
I was complimenting you.
Cute?
Say that again!
They just started all of a sudden.
I didn't know just calling her cute...
would make her so happy.
Girls…
There will now be a 20-minute break.
I'm going to run to the bathroom.
Okay, I'll watch our stuff.
He said I look cute!
Good thing it's still not too crowded.
Maybe I'll buy a drink.
I wonder if Hina wants anything.
Are you lost?
Did you get separated from your mom?
Oh, you fell down.
Let's go to the first aid station.
Everything's going to be okay.
Pain, pain, go away!
Is she lost?
Yeah.
She got separated from her mom.
I was going to take her to the main tent.
I'll come too.
Is it okay if I tag along?
I'm fine doing it myself.
I'm heading that way anyway.
What's your name?
Yume.
Yume-chan!
Hina's waiting for me,
but I can't just ignore them.
Wait!
We'll all go together!
Okay!
I usually hate mosquitos,
but today they came in handy!
It looks cute.
Chono-san?
Ito-kun.
I didn't know you'd be here.
Are you alone?
Oh, ofcourse not.
Are you here with your team?
No, I came with Taiki.
Taiki?
Kyo was supposed to come too,
but he came down with a cold!
And others turned me down,
as they already had plans.
Then how about we join you?
It'd be more fun in a big group.
We're standing over there, but I'd honestly love it if we could find a place to sit.
What do you think?
Yume-chan, are you thirsty?
I'm okay.
Well, we're almost there,
so let's keep going.
Okay.
Chinatsu-senpai sure gets along with kids.
I wouldn't have guessed that.
Probably because I always see her
talking to people older than her.
Sorry.
No problem.
Whoa, she's gorgeous.
Are you okay?
Karen!
Chii!
You know each other?
We were best friends and classmates...
through kindergarten and grade school.
What an incredible school!
Hello.
Hello!
And she's Haryu-kun's girlfriend.
Did you come with Haryu-kun?
Yeah, he's saved us seats.
That's right, he mentioned
his girlfriend was in showbiz.
By the way,
who are you?
My name is Taiki Inomata.
Haryu-senpai is always looking after me.
Inomata...? Are you that Taiki Inomata?
Oh, so you're him.
"That"?
What has Haryu-senpai
been saying about me?
Well…
He says you've got a lot of guts.
That sounds like a lie.
Anyway, I've got to get going.
I can see how
she's Haryu-senpai's girlfriend.
They're a good match, aren't they?
I just saw something interesting!
Kengo! Kengo!
I just saw something good.
What?
I ran into Taiki Inomata and Chii!
Huh? Just the two of them?
I guess technically
there were three of them.
It didn't look like a date,
but Taiki Inomata seemed like a good guy.
They should just date already.
There's no way Chii wants that.
You're right.
What?
If you slack off in your badminton...
it's over for us!
Yeah, I know.
I'll do my best on both fronts.
Good!
I feel like Chii is overthinking a lot of things.
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
A lost child?!
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
FIREWORKS
FESTIVAL
OPERATIONS
Her mom was just here!
She went out to look for her again.
I'll go and make an announcement.
I'll go look for her!
You guys stay here.
I'll be right back!
Let's wait inside.
RECEPTION
That lady before had
a really pretty yukata on!
Yeah, she did.
It had so many flowers
and was really cute!
Did you want to wear a yukata too?
Just a little.
But this shirt is pretty cute too, right?
It's one of my favorites.
Is it your Sunday best?
I'm surprised you know that phrase.
But my Sunday best would be my uniform.
Uniform?
I wear it when I play basketball, which I love.
I know basketball!
When I'm wearing my uniform,
I just want to be the coolest.
You're living with a first-year boy?
And his family.
It's basically the same.
Do you ever think of him like that?
Like as an actual guy...
and that you might like him?
Yeah.
But…
I'm looking for Yume-chan's mother!
Are you here?
I guess I'm just too awkward.
I probably couldn't wear a yukata.
I get that!
When I tried to put on my yukata...
it got all messed up.
So, Mommy ended up doing it for me.
It's tough, isn't it?
Hey!
Yume!
Mommy!
Where did you go?
She heard the announcement,
so I found her in no time.
That's good.
Thank you so much!
Let me repay in some way.
Don't worry about it!
No more getting separated, okay?
Yume!
Wait!
You can have it!
Yukata are hard, but this is easy!
Now you're pretty too!
But…
If it's not too much trouble,
I hope you will accept it!
Thank you!
Bye-bye!
Come on, let's go.
What are you laughing at?
Nothing.
How rude.
Yume-chan gave this to me, you know.
It looks good on you.
I actually hope you'll keep it on.
Stop laughing!
I mean, you're just staring at me.
You'll have to keep it on
until you get home.
It would break Yume-chan's heart
if she saw you without it.
Fine, I'll wear it until I get home.
She helped me look stylish, after all.
Then can I take a photo?
Permission denied.
"Permission"?
I bet if I told Chinatsu Senpai
that she was cute right now...
she would pause for a second...
before she giving me
an obligatory "thanks"...
and our fun time together would end.
It's again started.
Yeah.
We'd better get going.
Nagisa's waiting for me.
You're right.
Well, see you at home.
Yeah, see you there.
Crap! I left hina waiting longer than I'd planned.
Hurry up and get back here!
I need to apologize
for leaving her alone for so long.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
Sorry I took so long.
You owe me one.
Ah, shit!
Did you have any trouble while I was gone?
Nope, the vendor food is delish...
and the fireworks are beautiful!
Life's good!
We should come back next year.
Yeah.
And by that, I mean just the two of us.
Welcome back, Chinatsu.
What's with that hair clip?
It's a long story.
Wait, why do you look so sad?
Where will we be next year?
A year's long time.
How will we change?
That's what I was thinking about...
as I watched the fireworks burst
before fading into nothing.
Good morning.
Good morning, Chinatsu-chan.
I just finished making breakfast.
Taiki-kun's already up?
He's out running.
So much energetic this early in the morning.
He said the practice session he went to
made him realize he needs more stamina...
so he's going all out.
Natsu, it'd be better if you could've passed it to Nagi there.
She was pretty open.
Even when things get crazy,
try to remain calm.
Okay.
Look, I know the Inter-High are
right around the corner...
Try not to get too stiff and just be you.
We can all vouch for your skills.
Okay.
He won again.
We're no match for him anymore.
He is going to the Inter-High after all.
At that practice match the other day...
Haryu Senpai did better against Hyodo
than he did in the prefectural qualifiers.
The two slots to the Inter-High next year...
will go to Yusa and Haryu.
If you'd hit like that, you might've
scored more points against Yusa.
You want some?
Kyo, hit some up for me!
After what Hyodo told me...
I can't just lose!
Kyo, that's too fast.
Sorry, I need to get the shuttlecock.
Hey, Hina, could you…
Good luck.
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
That's what I'm talking about.
It's probably for the best.
What are you talking about?
Lunch break! Be back here by 1:20.
Okay!
I'll go open the windows upstairs.
Thanks.
Taiki?
Are you asleep?
He did go running this morning too.
So he sleeps holding his jacket...
DON'T USE IT
AS A BLANKET…
Hello?
Inomata-kun.
There's something I meant
to ask you before.
Are you going out with Chono-san?
Your answer…
might change how I feel about being your housemate.
Going to the fireworks festival together...
must mean that you are, right?
And Chono-san likes you after all.
If you are going out,
you could've just told me.
Are you going this year?
I'm going in a group.
You didn't need to lie
about going in a group.
Then I would've…
You know, it's lonesome being lied to.
I slept great.
Was somebody just here?
Must be imagining things.
How will you walk the path before you?
Shouldering the future that you envision
If everything was just smooth sailing
I wouldn't be able to feel anything
At the usual crosswalk, beyond the street of flowers
The air still dyes my breath white
Airplane contrails race across the sky
I chased after them before they disappeared
I know I sometimes get distracted
But let's go, even if we have to take a detour
The sound of us splitting food
is a memory we share
I still recall the song
we used to hum together
I found myself entirely consumed
Searching for an alternative to saying "bye bye"
Our golden days leading up to adulthood
They've passed us by before we knew it
Every moment was so precious
We didn't even have time to look back
I still ponder the words I couldn't say back then
Like that, we become dyed in blue