I've never seen someone cry like this before.
It's all because I stuck my nose where it didn't belong.
There should be extra in the gym, so would you fetch it for me?
If only I hadn't tried to get them alone together.
What should I say at a time like this?
If someone told me,
"There are better people out there..."
I feel like I'd say, "Yeah? Then bring them to me."
"It sucks, doesn't it?"
She'd probably think,
"Like you have any idea how I feel..."
Besides...
I don't know what heartbreak feels like.
I can't find the right words.
Tissues?
I thought it might get dirty at the barbecue!
I had a ton on me...
since I'm the manager.
You can use them if you like!
Thanks.
You can cry as hard as you want.
Okay...
You really like him, don't you?
Yeah.
I wonder if Inota has any idea
how strong her feelings are.
I wonder if any of the guys who asked me out...
liked me the same way she likes him.
Nope.. Probably not.
I'm sure it hurts but...
I'm jealous that she could like someone this much.
Should I just throw it away?
The feelings rolling around in my frozen hands
Don’t give up! Wish like you’re dancing
“There’s still time”
With a barefoot heart, I run forward
Blue    Box
I couldn’t say it—how I wanted things to stay like this just a little longer
I’m tired of pretending to be a fool, so maybe I’ll just quit
It’s probably an unrequited love, right? Truly a pathetic kind of love
It’s already too big to turn into a lie
Once again, I realize I love you, and it hurts
Maybe it’s a love that can’t be helped But it’s not a bad kind of love
shi,
I want to chase after your way of living, your dreams
I want to watch you
Mi
te
i
ta
Episode 25: Even so...
The returning bus arrives at 5 pm.
Let's have a game before then.
Make sure you pack up first.
That's a cute pattern.
It's my little sister's.
Ah.
I'm going on ahead to the gym.
Practice isn't for another half hour.
I wanna work on my serves.
Okay.
I'm not wrong.
If I didn't make my stance clear...
I said it's fine!
It's in.
Ah.
Even on the last day, you haven't slowed down a bit.
If this were enough to tire me out, I'd never win.
Oh, I like that!
Then...
mind if I ask for a game?
Love all play.
Let's start.
Kyo, could you go wake up nishida?
Okay.
MUTTER
I stuck my nose in where it didn't belong.
I never thought that would happen...
MUTTER
What's wrong?
Ah.
It has nothing to do with you, Kasahara-kun.
Please don't talk to me.
By any chance...
is this about Taiki and Chono-san?
Ah!
You know about that?
Just as I thought...
They'd been acting weird since yesterday.
I see. So Taiki gave his answer.
8-4
Damn it.
Time to say goodbye to this road.
Let's give the last practice our all!
I can't understand it.
It's the first time I'd heard of Inota having a crush on someone!
Ah...
Even so...
it's not everyday that you find a girl...
who'll love you that hard.
If he had no interest in her, then I could kinda get it.
But they get along so well as friends! Why can't it work?
About that... I feel the same way
Chono-san would probably get mad at me for saying this, but...
Huh?
I thought that they seemed happier as friends.
Ah...
Taiki tends to be the one chasing after a crush.
I don't think he's used to being on the receiving end.
The prerequisites for being a friend and a potential romantic partner...
really have a difference between them, I guess.
You can't do anything about it.
That's putting it mildly.
There's nothing else to say.
No matter what, we're on the outside looking in.
Taiki made his decision.
A straight shot.
A cross.
13-6
He's not letting me score at all.
Just when I was starting to think he was avoiding playing me...
He's gotten stronger again.
I want to catch up.
I don't want to lose.
If Haryu-senpai's going to get better...
then I can get better too.
Better.
Better!
Out.
Game set.
Thank you very much.
Huh!
One more game!
I thought you'd say that.
It's over. Done.
Besides, it's the last day of training camp. I'm tired.
You won and are not playing more.
Huh...
Honestly...
I was afraid to take you on.
Huh.
Haryu-senpai? Afraid?
Not cool, right?
I couldn't beat Hyodo-san in the end.
Then he went and left the team.
Even if it was a practice match, I lost to that first-year Yusa.
So if I lost to you on top of that...
I knew it'd crush my confidence.
Granted, I did win.
I'm glad we had that game.
It'd be pathetic if I kept running away!
Being scared of losing...
Having your petty pride get torn to shreds...
You gotta take all that in...
Chew it up, swallow it down, and crawl forward.
Cuz I think that's what strength is.
Everyone's so strong.
What're you talking about? You are too.
Chinatsu-senpai.
Taiki-kun, welcome back.
Same to you.
I'm home.
Right, welcome back.
Kinda weird, huh?
Chinatsu-senpai.
Hm?
Next break, why don't you and I go somewhere?
Where?
Huh?!
Where should we go?
Suggesting an amusement park would be too obvious.
And we already went to an aquarium.
What else is there... Shopping?
For something I've been wanting recently...
A tracksuit! I want to go shopping for a tracksuit!
Mine got all worn out during the training camp,
so I need a new one.
Ah...
How about it...?
Why did I suggest a tracksuit?
That's not charming at all.
Sure.
Really?!
In exchange, I wanted to check out this one cafe.
Can we go there too?
Ah...
Yeah. Of course.
Great!
How about next Saturday?
You have practice in the morning, right?
Yeah.
Then, next Saturday.
It's a date!
We're just shopping for a tracksuit, but...
it'll be our first outing since... the aquarium? the beach?
and Chinatsu-senpai seemed really down for it!
Time to put my best foot forward!
I'm gonna show her I'm a man!
It's my chance to tell her how I feel.
Hinachi, let's hang out!
Ah!
Right now?!
We've been sacrificing our youth for
the past 4 days and 3 nights!
So we gotta live it up!
But our stuff...
We'll leave it in a locker!
When the going gets tough, the best course of action is to stop thinking so much!
How is that even my face?
That's part of the fun!
You look good with red lips, Hinachi!
I've actually never worn lipstick.
Then let's go out to buy some next time!
Okay.
Air hockey! Let's play air hockey next!
I've never played before.
Huh? Then you're missing out on 20% of life!
20%...?
And Häagen's newest flavor accounts for over 50%.
What do I do? I'm missing on 70% then.
Then let's recover at least 20% right now!
Here goes!
Ah.
And that's how you do it.
You're not going to make this fun for me, huh?
Winner!
You've done this before?
Go! Go!
Eeeeeeeee!
Ah!
Hmm...
Good.
She looks like she's in better spirits.
Today's all about having loads of fun!
Huh? Ayame, is that you?
Who's this? A friend? She's cute.
My ex.
Ah...
What a waste. Why'd you break up?
Huh? Well, basically...
she's totally demanding.
Like about my attitude toward store clerks.
Always insisted to make it clear
if I'm ordering a M-size or a L-size.
I thought going out would be chill.
I thought he was awkward but nice.
You could say she was a total 180 from how I thought she'd be.
Guess I was a poor judge of character.
Let's go.
She hasn't lasted long with anyone else either.
Oh, and her older sister has a real hunk of a boyfriend.
She should learn from them and be a little more considerate.
You—
You have to say it like that. Otherwise, you can't live with yourself, right?
Huh?
If you really believe all that...
then you're a terrible judge of character.
By considering yourself the sane one and labeling the person who dumped you...
as crazy and in the wrong...
then you can protect yourself from the hurt and pain caused by...
all that time you spent liking them.
Ah...
Next time you show your face, I'm telling everyone all about your private account!
You—
I'm sorry.
Don't be, Hinachi.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Ah.
Oopsies, pardon me.
Manager, you did that on purpose...
Carry this to the storage for me, would ya?
Okay...
You've seemed mad ever since the training camp.
If I did something—
No. It's nothing.
It's definitely something.
It's just that...
Chono-san was crying.
Ah.
I know.
You know?!
I think she's a hundred times more hurt than you could ever hope to realize.
But you're acting like everything's fine...
That may be...
but with how things stand now I can't start a conversation with her.
I told her how I feel.
All I can do now is wait to see what she does.
I could never say something so presumptive as "Let's go back to being friends."
So Inota cares about her in his own way.
And yet... why?
I still can't understand...
why you would reject a girl like Hinachi.
Is the person you like really that captivating?
Ah.
Hey, they're calling for practice to start.
Okay.
What kind of question is that?
If I told her yes...
it would sound like Hina's not.
Ah.
What is it?
Nothing.
I bet you think that I'm meddling again.
Yep, that face tells me it's true.
It's true. I'm just an outsider.
But when I saw her like that...
ever since I saw her and wondered why, I told myself that...
I'm gonna tell everyone exactly what I think!
Because that's who I am!
Deal with it!
I don't care who they are!
I leave it up to them to decide how they take it!
It's true that, thanks to you...
Chono-san's a little better off thanks to you.
It's not bad having one person telling it like it is.
I feel like you're looking down on me.
No one's ever told me that before.
What?
What's that?
I'm lil Miss Bunny Ears from the culture festival.
By darkening my field of vision...
I can increase my concentration.
Okay, Hina. We'll skip your turn this time around.
Ah.
I wanna blow up the gym.
I don't wanna skip practice just because I got rejected.
But being in the same gym as Taiki and Chinatsu-senpai...
feels suffocating.
Kyo! You see my phone anywhere?
It was on the chair.
Oh, there it is! Thanks.
Hey, Taiki! Let's go grab something to eat.
Sorry, I've plans!
Good job today, guys!
What's with Taiki? He sure is in a hurry.
Must be a date.
What?!
I'm just kidding.
Knew it!
He's the last guy who'd betray me like that.
Wait. For real?
I didn't hear it directly from him or anything...
Then is it with...
Maybe.
Aha!
I was wondering how long he'd drag his feet.
Just going for it is much more his style.
In front of the planters, in front of the...
Ah.
That girl's pretty cute.
What were you looking at?
Um...
Just thinking that the clouds are moving quickly today.
The evening breeze, like it’s cooling down my flushed cheeks
Is gentle
The day I walked beside you will become something that lasts a lifetime
I know you’re being kind without thinking much of it
shii
But still, I can feel it clearly
Tte
chan
Ah, my focus jumps up
shuu
chuu
ryo
ku
With just one word, it gets hot
A tiny sign
Hon
no
chii
I end up dreaming
Why am I so happy?
shii
no
Why am I so sad?
shii
no
Even now, I gaze at you beside me
Your distant profile burned into my memory, ah
Today, I still can’t reach you
Though you’re so close
Brought to you by [KawaSubs]
Thank You for being with us
on this beautiful journey