Should I just throw it away?
The feelings rolling around in my frozen hands
Don’t give up! Wish like you’re dancing
“There’s still time”
With a barefoot heart, I run forward
Blue    Box
I couldn’t say it—how I wanted things to stay like this just a little longer
I’m tired of pretending to be a fool, so maybe I’ll just quit
It’s probably an unrequited love, right? Truly a pathetic kind of love
It’s already too big to turn into a lie
Once again, I realize I love you, and it hurts
Maybe it’s a love that can’t be helped But it’s not a bad kind of love
shi,
I want to chase after your way of living, your dreams
I want to watch you
Episode 14: What's the Connection?
About tomorrow's second round game...
We're up against last year's champs, Minatozaki Academy.
Honestly, it's gonna be a tough game...
but they are not unbeatable.
I want each one of you to stay focused.
Okay!
Nagisa! Chinatsu!
We are counting on you tomorrow.
We won the first round, all thanks
to the points you scored.
That was due to the assists
you Senpais gave us.
Then, next time try to do it
without the assists.
That was sorta harsh.
By the way, Chinatsu, did you hear?
Yoshitani-senpai and Koike-senpai are...
leaving the team after
the Inter-High is over.
What?!
They want to focus on entrance exams.
So we have to make sure...
we can keep them on the basketball team for as long as possible.
I didn't hear it directly from them though.
It's just a rumour...
She rolled up like a pill bug!
Let me explain!
Chinatsu’s     pressure...
It's like our final game of Junior High.
reaches it's        limit...
Chinatsu-san, you don't have to bear it all on your shoulders.
I can't.
She doesn't usually vent it out...
Well, cannot blame Chinatsu...
She came all this way to Inter-High, even leaving your family behind.
Even though she's only a second-year,
she's expected to be the main scorer.
That's a lot to deal with for one person.
Nagisa.
You enjoy basketball, right?
Of course.
I do too.
Until now, I've always had this anxiety in a corner of my mind...
But after playing that first match and winning it...
the adrenaline rush I got...
I get it.
It's because of all the practice we've put in.
Getting passes from Yoshitani-senpai...
Having Koike-senpai's screen free
me up so I could take a shot.
And having you, Nagisa, grab the rebound if I miss.
I thought about how I wanted to keep playing basketball for the rest of my life.
That's impossible, you know.
Come on! Get up already!
You could let me stay down a little longer.
You can't play basketball if you're not standing up!
Your wish ribbon would cry seeing you like this!
Huh?
I'll be okay. I'll do what I have to do tomorrow.
You better do it.
Taiki, that court's available!
Coming!
So Hyodo-san ended up winning.
At least Haryu lost to the eventual champion.
Just don't bring it up to him.
Now only the girls basketball team is left at the Inter-High.
I think they have a game at 4 pm today.
By the way, what about Chuno-san?
Did you hear about her results?
I haven't heard from her.
I contacted her before the event, but...
Hey, you guys!
They're doing maintenance on the gym today...
so we have to clear out of here by four.
Okay!
I haven't forgotten anything, have I?
I wonder if Chinatsu-senpai is doing warm-ups right about now.
That's a bad omen!
I have to at least make one shot by four!
Huh?
Omen or not...
Chinatsu-senpai will still make her shots.
After all, she practiced so much everyday...
She's one year older to me...
Does things at her own pace...
Stays strangely distant...
and I never know what she's thinking.
She can also be surprisingly childish at times...
She worries too much about being considerate.
Plus, she hates losing.
When she's playing basketball, she looks so incredibly cool.
That's my senpai...
I love...
Whoaaaa, what am I doing?!
Muttering a practice confession is so cringey!
I didn't want to hear myself sound so serious!
And somewhere so public!
Even though I can't even tell that to her face!
Now I'm all depressed about a bunch of things...
What are you yelling about all by yourself?
Hina!
The gym's off-limits for the rest of the day.
I know that.
Had to report my Inter-High results to the principal.
Our school's pretty annoying when it comes to stuff like that.
So how did you do?
Taiki.
Treat me to some Taiyaki.
Tai..?
We will now begin...
Minatozaki Academy versus Eimei High.
Let's have a good game!
I thought taiyaki in summer was weird, but...
that's how they serve it...
Sweet bean paste and soft serve ice cream go perfect together!
The Inter-High is over,
so I'm rewarding myself.
Ahh~ This hits the spot~
She hasn't mentioned anything
about her results...
Maybe things didn't go well?
Otherwise, she would've told me right away.
Even this taiyaki looks like stress eating....
By the way, I got third place.
Third place?
My Inter-High results.
I just realized I hadn't told you.
Don't drop that so casually...
Third place is amazing!
You means third nationally, right?
And you think I'm satisfied with that?
I guess not?
It's a better score than before...
and I can see how much I've improved.
So next time I'll go even higher.
You're not all full of yourself shows how you incredible are, Hina.
But from an outside perspective, third place is really impressive.
So let me be happy for you.
Congratulations!
Thanks.
Hmm?
Something felt unusual about her expression.
Let's go eat in that park over there!
Wait for me!
They should be in the third quarter now.
Minatozaki
Eimei
That was delicious~
Thanks for the treat!
You're welcome.
The swings are free!
Well, I'm glad she's having fun.
Stop!
Huh? Why?
Your panties were almost seen by me...
What?
I've got compression shorts on!
That's not the issue!
You're a girl! You ought to be more careful!
This is rare.
You treating me like a girl.
Of course, I would.
You are a girl after all.
Are you worried about the time?
Ah... no, not really.
Could it be Chinatsu-senpai's match today?
Yeah, it is.
They should be starting
the fourth quarter right now.
I heard their opponent is last year's champion.
So today's game is really important.
I see.
Not that.. I can do anything about it...
Ah! In that case, let's have a shoe-throwing contest!
What's the connection?
Chinatsu-senpai's fighting hard, so I figured that you should fight hard too, Taiki.
Don't look at my panties.
I'm not.
If you lose, you have to tell an embarrassing story that you've never told anyone.
What? There's a penalty?
By the way, I know about the first-year training camp incident in Junior High.
Stop it!
Okay, you go first, Taiki.
If she's having fun, then fine by me...
Somehow, today...
she seems a bit unusual.
That flew pretty high.
Not so fast.
This game demands distance, not height.
What, so you're an expert now?
So, my turn next!
Natsu!
Can you kick it out of the park?
Go for it!
I got this.
I've never said this to anybody, but...
I'm in love.
Minatozaki
Eimei
I am not good enough.
Not at all.
I like you, Taiki.
You mean...
like romantically?
Romantically.
You thought we were just good friends, so you let your guard down, didn't you?
Listen, I'm just as shocked as you are.
To think that I'd feel this way about Taiki...
How about that?! Surprise!
What sort of face is that?
I didn't expect that at all.
I really don't know what to think.
This is the first time anyone's ever confessed their love to me.
Honestly, it got kind of embarrassed.
Totally out of the blue.
I know you like Chinatsu-senpai...
so I don't need a response right away.
I just thought that, if I didn't tell you, then nothing would ever change.
From now on, don't see me as a friend...
but as a girl who's in love with you.
Well, now that that's done, I'm heading home.
Huh?
When I win first place next time, I'd would like a parfait!
Ah.. Hina!
It's so nerveracking to have someone confess their feelings to you!
Hina likes me?
Was there any sign of that?
And since when?
Could it be... even at the fireworks festival...
Say it again!
Even back then...
she liked me... just imagining that...
hits me right in the chest.
Thinking about it, I was pretty awful to her, wasn't I?
Well then, at that time too...
Taiki, that's...
what makes you so cool.
She's a good person...
as a friend...
as an athlete, and as a human being.
Easy to talk to, and hardworking.
Worthy of respect.
And someone like that l-likes...
Stop doing it outside.
What does it look like I am doing?
Working out.
I'm not.
I'm home~
I don't want my mom seeing me...
contemplating my love life.
By the way, we got a call.
Huh?
Chinatsu-chan's team lost.
Make sure to tell her she did
a good job when she's back.
I will.
What's with it...
I haven't done anything wrong...
Why do I feel so guilty...
How am I supposed to act when I meet her next time?
I don't know.
Oh, good. The rhythmic gymnastics team's taking today off.
I'm not sure I'd be able to talk properly with Hina if I saw her right now.
I need some time...
Okay!
What are you looking at?!
I can't help it! That's the entrance I use too!
I thought you had today off!
Just had to take care of something.
Well, you could've said a Hi!
That's hard to do right now!
Why?
Why, well...
Oh, right. You just keep that up, Taiki.
Your heart will skip a beat
every time you see me.
My heart's not skipping...
Even if it's not...
just remember...
I'm in love with you, Taiki.
There! Your heart just skipped a beat.
It didn't!
Good, good. Looks like my confession worked like a charm.
Hey.. Keep your voice down!
The evening breeze, like it’s cooling down my flushed cheeks
Is gentle
The day I walked beside you will become something that lasts a lifetime
I know you’re being kind without thinking much of it
shii
But still, I can feel it clearly
Tte
chan
Ah, my focus jumps up
shuu
chuu
ryo
ku
With just one word, it gets hot
A tiny sign
Hon
no
chii
I end up dreaming
Why am I so happy?
shii
no
Why am I so sad?
shii
no
Even now, I gaze at you beside me
Your distant profile burned into my memory, ah
Today, I still can’t reach you
Though you’re so close