By the way...
I told Taiki that I have feelings for him.
Is that so?
Uh, I mean!
Since you're living with him...
I figured it'd be best to let you know.
But it's not like I want you to act differently around me or anything.
If that's what this is about right now,
I'm living somewhere else.
My grandpa has to undergo surgery.
So my mom came back temporarily...
and I'll be with her for a month until his surgery's over.
Oh.
I had no idea!
I hope your grandfather's surgery goes smoothly!
I'm gonna go and take care of some other stuff.
Take your time with the copier!
See ya!
Should I just throw it away?
The feelings rolling around in my frozen hands
Don’t give up! Wish like you’re dancing
“There’s still time”
With a barefoot heart, I run forward
Blue    Box
I couldn’t say it—how I wanted things to stay like this just a little longer
I’m tired of pretending to be a fool, so maybe I’ll just quit
It’s probably an unrequited love, right? Truly a pathetic kind of love
It’s already too big to turn into a lie
Once again, I realize I love you, and it hurts
Maybe it’s a love that can’t be helped But it’s not a bad kind of love
shi,
I want to chase after your way of living, your dreams
I want to watch you
Mi
te
i
ta
Episode 17: Of Course, I Want to See It
Thank you very much.
Taiki. You've gotten really good!
You're nice and relaxed. You look so comfortable out there.
Thank you.
Really? I don't feel that way.
Surely I'm scoring more points than I used to.
And I can feel that I'm moving better.
So, why do I feel...
so anxious?
Huddle up!
It's taken a while, but we finally have a practice match this Saturday.
Against whom?
Calm down.
It'll be against Sajikawa High.
Ah...
That guy...
For real? Nice.
But they don't have Hyodo-san.
Even without the third-years, they're still tough.
If we can't beat Sajikawa...
there's no way we'll make the Inter-High next year.
Yes, sir!
Works perfectly for me.
I've been wanting to battle that first-year.
Yusa-kun?
Yeah.
He's got the face of someone who wears turtlenecks in winter.
What kind of face is that?
What're you so nervous about?
You've already lost to him once, so go at it like you've got nothing to lose.
Haryu, you're not helping.
I'll work on it.
Taiki. I heard the news.
A practice match on Saturday, huh?
Run, read your lines, or talk. Not all three at once.
It's more efficient this way.
And I hear moving around helps you remember stuff better.
How clever of you.
We don't have gymnastics on Saturday. But I'll be at school to practice the play.
I wanna come cheer you on during your game.
You don't have to.
It's just a practice match.
But it's a significant opponent, right?
Yeah...
And it's someone you've lost to before.
That's right. Hina saw it in person.
If that's your opponent, then I'll need to embolden you, right?
What an outdated way to say it.
Besides.
I want to see the person I like trying his best.
Why'd you have to say that out of nowhere?!
Don't turn around so suddenly!
Watch where you're going, or you'll run into something!
Ow! Ow!
All right already!
Good morning.
Morning.
Whoa!
Oh. Good morning.
Morning.
You seem really motivated!
No, it's nothing.
Is this for the upcoming practice match?
Word sure gets around fast in this gymnasium.
Saturday, was it?
I have practice in the morning, so I'll come watch later.
Huh!
Hm?
You don't have to do that.
But it sounds fun.
It's not like it's an official match.
So there's no point in you seeing it.
Come on. Of course, I want to see it.
I want to see the person I like trying his best.
Hm?
Oh! It's nothing!
It's because of what Hina said.
I've got no right to stop you.
That's right. So I'm going.
I've got to watch my practice buddy when he's being so fearless.
Huh?
Taiki, what've you been eating?
You've gotten better again.
I'm not eating anything different.
I still have a ton of stuff to work on.
One step ahead of me.
That was exactly how it felt.
Did you hear about Yusa from Sajikawa High?
He won against a retired player from Japan team.
So he was going up against a pro? Isn't he still only a first-year?
He's a beast.
Tanigawa! Let's play another game!
Again?
Taiki!
Please play against me...
Don't even think about running away.
If you lose, you have to hold a plank for 5 mins.
But he's on a winning streak.
Don't we need to knock him down a peg?
He'll be fine. Even when he wins, he still doesn't look satisfied.
Sometimes, even if people think highly of you...
you can still refuse to acknowledge yourself.
But he's applying himself to practice and improving.
He wants to beat that first-year at Sajikawa.
That's a high bar to clear.
Efforts that don't feel like they're leading to growth must feel tough, right?
If that's the case, then give him some advice.
Nah, I won't.
I'll be battling to secure a slot at the Inter-High next year.
So I need my junior to struggle as much as possible.
You're so immature.
Then I'll just have step in as captain...
Nishida!
Yes, sir!
Did you sign the form for the club's expenses?
Ack! Sorry.
I was thinking of doing it later...
and then I got busy in the school festival.
Really, sorry...
The shine on this apple is great!
I bought a fake one at the dollar store and then Hina repainted it.
She said something about the color not being rich enough.
By the way, where is Hina?
I think she's in the classroom practicing for the play.
I see.
Hina, can I help with any—
She's dead!
Am not.
I was practicing for the play!
Ah.
The final scene where Snow White wakes up.
This is the only scene where I'm not sure how I should act.
I'll practice with you then.
Huh?
It'll be easier to visualize if there's someone else.
True, but...
"Wake up..."
(The prince kisses her)
No way I'm doing that!
I know that already!
So what part don't you get?
What kind of face would someone
who just came back from the dead make?
That's a good question.
Plus, she was tricked by the queen...
to eat the poisoned apple.
If Snow White knew that...
Oh ho ho ho!~
Now I'm the fairest in the land!
Queen cannot be forgiven!
Your head is mine!
Draw the sword!
That's too vengeful.
Oh, I got it.
When she wakes up, Prince is there, so her heart skips a beat.
Who the heck are you?
WHO
THE
HECK
ARE
YOU?
WHO
THE
HECK
ARE
YOU?
WHO
THE
HECK
ARE
YOU?
WHO
THE
HECK
ARE
YOU?
WHO
THE
HECK
ARE
YOU?
WHO
THE
HECK
ARE
YOU?
WHO
THE
HECK
ARE
YOU?
WHO
THE
HECK
ARE
YOU?
Too much cautious.
I knew it. This isn't working.
What do I do? It's the most important scene.
I have to deliver my best for the finale.
Being resurrected from the dead...
Maybe like how you feel after a big test?
You're really amazing, Hina.
Even though you could pull this off without overthinking it...
You're really worried about it...
and always walking around with the script.
If it were me, I'd just put on a simple smile.
When I take something on, I want to give it my all.
Same as you, Taiki.
Huh?
One minute you're doing stuff for the play in the classroom...
and the next, you're at badminton practice in the gym.
Taiki, you're also doing great.
Hmm.
Hmm..
I mean everybody says so.
That, though. Let's get practicing!
It might be best to just go with the flow on this one.
Then I'll read the line that comes before.
I personally have a lot on my plate, but...
If I'm able to do my job, then I'm glad.
"Snow White. Please wake up..."
There.
You've been kissed.
Hina?
Is this part of your act?
It's not.
I imagined I really did share a kiss with you, Taiki.
Huh?!
Wanna do it?
"Wake up..."
(The prince kisses her)
Wanna do it for real?
No, I don't.
I know it.
I'd be way more freaked out if you'd said "Yes"!
But...
I still got your heart pounding, right?
This is another attack strategy of the Hina-sama!
Guess I'll see what everyone else is doing.
Ah...
I like you...
Romantically...
I hope you remember that I like you, Taiki.
Ah...
Game Set!
Why?
Even though I can beat other players, the gap in our scores is even bigger now.
There are still too many flaws.
At the very least...
Yusa-kun was better than this.
Taiki.
The shuttlecocks of someone who has no confidence...
won't beat me.
What?
It's not that I'm lacking in confidence.
As expected from Chono-san!
Not exactly...
Natsu!
Nice!
I'm just a coward.
What?!
Class 2-D is making curry samples?!
I'm gonna go get some!
I hate curry.
People like you actually exist?!
♪ Curry! Curry! ♪
♪ Let's eat curry! Let's drink curry! ♪
Chi, good work!
Good job!
The basketball team's got night practice?
Nope. I had to stay late for the Culture Festival.
You do it all, don't you? Aren't you busy enough with basketball?
You sure are quite stoic.
I wouldn't look at it like that.
Every morning, you're always the first one in.
And you're super serious.
No, other people besides me come. Inomata-kun from the badminton team is here early too.
I wouldn't call Taiki stoic...
so much as committed.
I heard they got Fank-Furters over there!
What?! Let's go!
What's the difference?
You are a sadist, he's a masochist.
He has someone he wants to win against since he's made that his goal...
He can't stop focusing on his shortcomings.
And he stops giving himself credit.
But there's no reason to keep living like...
crossing a desert without water.
He's so committed to what he has to work on...
that he's forgotten to stay hydrated.
He feels like he needs to leap forward as fast as possible and I get that.
There are some people who would give up even if they had enough water.
But...
if you don't want to give up, you've got to keep putting one foot in front of the other.
The hardest thing in the world is standing still.
Yeah. You've got a point.
Anyway.
I'm headed off to night practice.
Haryu-kun.
If you're that worried about him...
then maybe you should give him some hydration.
It's your duty as his senpai.
Nah, I'm the one who could use some.
Hey, Taiki!
Yes?
You're eating curry?!
Captain Nishida gave it to me.
So, it was him.
He's a great Team Captain!
I thought we could practice, but I'll ask Kyo instead.
Hey! Hold on a minute!
Ah!
Oh, could I have that water? The curry was spicy.
No way.
Aw, come on.
Where're the shuttles?
Got them here.
Someone call the coach!
I'm off!
Right now...
I'm just a coward.
When hina told me she liked me and said I didn't have to give her an answer...
I didn't know how to respond.
Even with sports, I'm the only one...
who's not making any progress.
So...
Excuse me.
Ah!
Could you show me where the gym is?
At least...
The evening breeze, like it’s cooling down my flushed cheeks
Is gentle
The day I walked beside you will become something that lasts a lifetime
I know you’re being kind without thinking much of it
shii
But still, I can feel it clearly
Tte
chan
Ah, my focus jumps up
shuu
chuu
ryo
ku
With just one word, it gets hot
A tiny sign
Hon
no
chii
I end up dreaming
Why am I so happy?
shii
no
Why am I so sad?
shii
no
Even now, I gaze at you beside me
Your distant profile burned into my memory, ah
Today, I still can’t reach you
Though you’re so close
Brought to you by [KawaSubs]