Is it just me, or is Yusa even stronger than before?
He's gotten bigger too.
And yet he's even faster now.
Could any of our second-years even stand a chance against him?
Thank you
Thank you very much.
very
much
You're in perfect form, Yusa.
But that game just now, you could've stopped him from getting five points.
When you returned in the latter half...
I would've smashed it right back at him.
Don't sleep!
I don't have time to hear all this from you, Yakushiji-senpai.
You going to sleep proves you've got time!
It's called taking a break.
I want to conserve my energy and be in perfect shape when I take that guy on.
You mean Haryu-kun?
No doubt he's the strongest Eimei's got.
I hate to admit it, but he did go to the Inter-High.
He aims for the absolute worst spots.
So he's fun to go up against.
Huh? That's not fun at all!
Are you stupid?
Yusa!
Sorry that it's back-to-back, but you've got another game.
Against who?
Some guy named Inomata. He's a first-year like you.
Inomata...
Thanks for the play.
Oh, right. He's the guy who showed me to the gym earlier.
Should I just throw it away?
The feelings rolling around in my frozen hands
Don’t give up! Wish like you’re dancing
“There’s still time”
With a barefoot heart, I run forward
Blue    Box
I couldn’t say it—how I wanted things to stay like this just a little longer
I’m tired of pretending to be a fool, so maybe I’ll just quit
It’s probably an unrequited love, right? Truly a pathetic kind of love
It’s already too big to turn into a lie
Once again, I realize I love you, and it hurts
Maybe it’s a love that can’t be helped But it’s not a bad kind of love
shi,
I want to chase after your way of living, your dreams
I want to watch you
Mi
te
i
ta
Episode 18: I Know
All right!
Ah...
May the best win.
Let's play.
Oh! He's up.
It looks like they're just about to start.
Uh, what're you doing?
Didn't you promise him you'd cheer him on?
I said I'd come watch.
I never said anything about cheering.
It's the same.
This is the revenge match with the guy Taiki lost to earlier, right?
Yeah.
I know that, but...
I don't want to see Taiki like that.
Back then too...
I didn't know what to say to him.
Why're you assuming he'll lose this time too?
Ah!
I am not saying he'll lose.
Oh. They've started.
You don't have to worry about what to say to Taiki.
I think you should watch this for your own sake, Hina.
Oh, he's returning them! He's doing it!
Huh!
Hm?
Everyone's playing well.
Apparently, they're up against the best in the prefecture.
Ah! He scored a point.
Which court are you watching?
The second from the back left.
Let me see.
Alright!
Hey. I'm sorry if I'm wrong about this, but I gotta ask..
Hm?
Err... But then again...
What is it?
By any chance...
On your birthday, were you with him?
That night, before you hung up, I heard a guy's voice for a second.
So, you gonna tell me you two are dating?
Say something! Don't leave me in the dark!
You don't have to be shy just because you're in the same gym!
That's not it.
The family that I'm staying with...
is Taiki-kun's.
Wha...
Our moms know each other and they happened to have a room available.
So...
Grab
Huh...
Are you stupid?!
I was thrilled that you were able to stay in Japan, but...
why would you live with a guy your own age?!
What if something happened?!
A great historical figure once said that all men are beasts!
My own little brother had his ◎◎◎ go ×××!
Something like what?
Nothing happened.
That was a loaded pause.
Fine. It's not like I know the whole situation...
but I wished you'd at least told me sooner.
Sorry about that.
Ah.
The game just started, but his opponent's already dictating the pace.
Still...
I don't know how you could even consider living with a stranger like that.
It's not like he was a total stranger.
Ah, shit!
He can keep a rally going, but he can't finish.
If he can't get the point, then it's meaningless.
Haryu, you could be a little kinder to your junior.
I've already seen you lose!
Hey!
This might be a practice match, but if you don't grow from this...
you'll get left behind again, Taiki.
I could punch myself for having said so nonchalantly...
that I wanted to go to the Inter-High.
I still have to be better than Yusa.
When I won that set against Haryu-senpai, I let it get to my head.
Because of that, everyone else went to the Inter-High...
while i just watched.
And on top of that...
I was happy.
Surprised but happy.
Still somewhere in my heart...
I thought, "me?"...
Hey, is he okay? Your housemate, I mean.
His movements look rough.
Like he's getting desperate.
I'm sure he's fine, as long as he's still standing.
Back then...
Chinatsu-chan said they lost.
When Chinatsu-senpai was feeling down...
No, you idiot! Not there!
What's he doing?!
That's where Yusa excels.
Yusa's making Taiki dance for him.
I was happy that she turned to me for help.
I wanted to cheer her up, but...
Who do I think I am?
Ah!
You all right?
Yeah.
Badminton is quite hard.
It really tires you out.
Keeping up with a shuttlecock moving that fast.
The Taiki I know...
usually looks like he's enjoying himself...
I've never seen him looking like this before.
Out!
What a waste. That was his chance.
Missing the shot after a long rally can affect you mentally.
Because of the first game, his stamina's already waning.
I'm starting to understand...
what Taiki-kun was saying back then.
When I stand alone on the court...
it feels like all the responsibility is on me.
I know how hard he worked at all those morning practices.
At the beginning, I just thought
"There's that kid who's always here."
But he came literally every day.
Since he always showed up so early, I'd come even earlier the next day to beat him.
Taiki-kun said that, but...
Chinatsu-senpai...
you were practicing even after your last game of Junior High, right?
I saw him too.
The very next day, after Taiki-kun's own final game, he was also practicing.
Fight!
You got this!
I can see it!
It's uncanny.
He's getting faster and faster.
Even on rainy days.
Taiki, fight!
Taiki!
Huh!
No matter the day...
he never stopped moving forward.
I know!
It's a scramble for the final set too.
It feels like he has awakened.
That kid wasn't even supposed to be a big deal.
Even though this means he's got another rival during next year's Inter-High...
Yusa sure looks like he's enjoying himself.
That's one serious rally.
Taiki is definitely keeping up.
In fact, I'd say Taiki's the one who's...
Taiki won!
Great job!
Nice fight!
Amazing! Inomata-kun won!
Okay, then let's get back to practicing for the play!
Huh? You're not going to say anything to him?
Hina!
Nice, Taiki!
To be honest, I didn't think you'd win.
But that was a good game.
Honestly, I didn't think you'd win. But you've come a long way.
Taiki, thank your opponent.
Coming!
Thank you.
Listen.
I'm still not satisfied.
Then let's have another—
You dummy.
You're about to collapse.
You too, Yusa.
After you rest, you're going up against me.
Phew. I can't even move.
I am moving forward.
I won!
You'll catch a cold if you fall asleep there.
Ah, Chinatsu-senpai!
That reminds me. She said she'd come watch.
Right or left? Which do you want?
Eh?
They're gifts for you.
One in right hand, another in left.
Okay, right one then.
Right.
Thanks. I was just feeling thirsty.
So what was in the left hand?
Another Pocari.
Isn't it the same?
It's times like this that her childish nature really shows.
They aren't same.
The one in my right hand was charged with a special appreciation power.
No wonder my tiredness disappeared.
So, like, Pocari...
normally, when you drink it, it's super-sweet.
But when you drink it after a workout, it doesn't taste all that sweet. Why is that?
It's cuz you're tired.
I can agree with that but still...
Well, you've been sweating so much. You have to replenish your nutrients.
I'm sorry you had to see that embarrassing display...
Don't apologize for that.
You looked cool out there.
Thank you.
But the reason I won was also
thanks to you, Chinatsu-senpai.
Those daily morning drills you did.
How you ran your heart out during practice.
Because I saw you doing all that...
I ended up realizing I could do a lot more than I thought.
So I'm going to keep learning from you and do my best, Chinatsu-senpai!
Today I won by the skin of my teeth.
Next time, I want a big lead!
Good.
Ah, this song...
The school orchestra is practicing for the culture festival.
The event's coming right up.
Compared to August, the temperature's cooled down a lot too.
yawarakai hibi ga
nami no oto ni somaru
maboroshiyo samenaide
Surprisingly, you isn't very good at singing...
Eh!
No need to say that aloud!
Sorry, sorry.
I'm happy I got to see another new side to Chinatsu-senpai.
Are you good at singing, Taiki?
I'm average.
Average doesn't mean much.
But it's true.
Haryu
-senpai's
good.
TYPICAL
MUSICAL
STAR
Kyo won't
sing in front
of others.
Chono-san's really good.
She certainly seems so.
By the way, Chono-san came to watch too.
Oh. She said that she'd come when she had a break from practicing...
Wanna do it for real?
But...
But really...
it's thanks to everyone's support that I won!
Calm down, calm down. It's not like we did it for real.
How's the play coming along?
I saw you guys building the set out in the schoolyard.
It's going as well as can be expected.
Nice.
I look forward to it.
Please do. The original stuff they added in is pretty funny too.
What about the kiss?
We didn't!
Huh?
Uh...
I was just wondering how you'd pull it off in the play.
Ah... They'll just pretend! Pretend!
Huh? Taiki, where'd you go?
Ah, I gotta go back!
Okay.
Thanks for today.
You're welcome.
Let's head home.
This way, over here.
Yusa-kun!
You forgot this. This is yours, right?
Oh, thanks.
It's fine.
Inomata!
See ya!
Inomata-kun!
Yes?
So is your name made from the "ino" of "wild boar"
and the "mata" of "hip joint"?
Yeah.
If I don't convert a name into its kanji, I can't really remember it.
Okay, bye. Inomata-kun.
Hmm, bye.
Next time, we'll battle in a real match.
Haryu-senpai, I'll trade with you.
Don't worry about him.
Why? What's up?
Haryu just lost to Yusa-kun.
He's in a bad mood.
Taiki, time for dinner!
Taiki!
He's probably asleep.
But his food will get cold.
Let him sleep. He had that practice match today.
Seems like it really took a lot out of him.
It's the Inter-High qualifiers. What an exciting game!
Intense Rally, Oops!
Oh! Inomata won!
Victory goes to Eimei High's Taiki Inomata!
My loss, Inomata-kun.
You annihilated me.
Let's do it again sometime!
Okay, how about right now?
Eh?
Taiki-kun!
Chinatsu-senpai!
You were watching?
Yep. Congrats on winning.
You looked cool out there.
Thank you.
Now... Time for a celebratory kiss.
What?!
Wait...
We can't.
Ch- Chinatsu-senpa...
YANK
I won't let that happen!
Hina!
Ah.
What a dream...
The evening breeze, like it’s cooling down my flushed cheeks
Is gentle
The day I walked beside you will become something that lasts a lifetime
I know you’re being kind without thinking much of it
shii
But still, I can feel it clearly
Tte
chan
Ah, my focus jumps up
shuu
chuu
ryo
ku
With just one word, it gets hot
A tiny sign
Hon
no
chii
I end up dreaming
Why am I so happy?
shii
no
Why am I so sad?
shii
no
Even now, I gaze at you beside me
Your distant profile burned into my memory, ah
Today, I still can’t reach you
Though you’re so close
Brought to you by [KawaSubs]