boyaketa roku toboshidakedo
omoikomi no koi ni ochita
This is pretty cool!
Yeah!
"Yeah!"...
She said "Yeah!"...
Up until now, the Cultural Festival
has been so much fun...
Huh...
Eh...
Ah...
Hmm...
No way!!
Green Room
I can't do it!
How can you say that?
You already put on the costume!
Green Room
You made me put it on!
Inomata, we need you.
The audience is waiting for you.
For the replacement?!
That's right! There's Kyo! He knows all the lines...
The festival committee grabbed him.
Ah...
Please.
Inomata, you've watched the whole production.
Can't you take over? You're our only hope to keep all that hard work from going to waste.
I've seen them practice.
So I know how hard this is.
Fine! I'll do it!
I'll play the prince!
Well said, Taiki!
That's our leader!
Somebody get me the script!
Yes, take it.
Even if I forget my lines, help cover for me!
I will!
Should I just throw it away?
The feelings rolling around in my frozen hands
Don’t give up! Wish like you’re dancing
“There’s still time”
With a barefoot heart, I run forward
Blue    Box
I couldn’t say it—how I wanted things to stay like this just a little longer
I’m tired of pretending to be a fool, so maybe I’ll just quit
It’s probably an unrequited love, right? Truly a pathetic kind of love
It’s already too big to turn into a lie
Once again, I realize I love you, and it hurts
Maybe it’s a love that can’t be helped But it’s not a bad kind of love
shi,
I want to chase after your way of living, your dreams
I want to watch you
Mi
te
i
ta
Episode 20: As One of Her Closest Friends
You can do it, Taiki!
It's true I've seen them rehearse plenty of times.
I may not get every single word...
But I think I have most of the script memorized.
So I'll be fine...
Yeah, right!
The most I've ever done was...
play the keyboard harmonica at a recital in elementary school!
I can't even recite "She sells seashells by the seashore" properly!
Is this the ordeal that Nishida-senpai was talking about?!
Maybe I can ad-lib my way through.
Then distract them with a song if I blank.
Well...
"Wake up..."
(The prince kisses her)
There's this problem too...
"Wake up..."
(The prince kisses her)
I know...
that I can just fake it.
But it's impossible not to feel embarrassed.
Wanna do it for real?
I gotta be as cool as I can about it.
I'll get a seat smack dab in the middle.
Ah....
Chinatsu-senpai is coming to watch.
Now I'll just look like a liar again.
And I can't just tell her not to come.
Chinatsu Kano
Thanks for coming!
Chi, over here!
Thanks for saving me a seat.
As you requested, we're smack dab in the middle.
There sure are a lot of people here.
It was empty when our class was on stage.
Ah, it's a fortune teller.
Hello.
The guys in our class...
said they were coming to see the girl from rhythmics.
Oh, is she that cute?
Which one of us is cuter?
Go on, mister, tell me.
You, Karen-sama.
She's got him whipped.
Well, they needed a reason.
Normally you wouldn't go to see a play unless you know someone who's in it.
Do you know someone in it, Kengo?
He's not gonna act, but he led the project and handled the costumes...
He's gonna act.
Taiki Inomata will be playing the Prince.
Taiki?
The Prince?
I suddenly cannot wait to see this.
Get the camera ready.
Huh?
But how do you know, Kano?
A substitution due to an injury...
So everyone's talking about it!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
KawaSubs
Taiki Inomata
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
GOOD BUCK!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
GOOD BUCK!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
GOOD BUCK!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
GOOD BUCK!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
GOOD BUCK!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
GOOD BUCK!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
GOOD BUCK!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
GOOD BUCK!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
GOOD BUCK!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
GOOD BUCK!!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
GOOD BUCK!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
GOOD BUCK!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
GOOD BUCK!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
GOOD BUCK!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
GOOD BUCK!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
GOOD BUCK!!
I suddenly got
roped into
acting!
Please spare me
your judgment!!
GOOD BUCK!!
Hey, Inomata!
Did you set up the confetti ball?
You know, for the announcement of best class.
I did! I finished it just in time this morning.
And I hurried to hang it up.
Well then, fine.
The next act is a play by first-year students.
A fairy tale that everyone knows...
with a bit of twist.
There was a little hiccup, but you never know what'll happen during the performance.
So let's have fun and get through it!
Fight!
Yeah!
Good luck, Taiki.
Don't lose, Taiki.
You can do it, Taiki.
Thanks for the championship level support.
I've gone through the whole thing.
As long as I keep calm on stage, I should be fine.
I imagined what it would be like to actually do it with you.
I gotta stop thinking about that.
Stand up straight...
Aren't you a little too nervous about this?
Just give it up already!
Give it up? How are you not nervous?
Did you forget who I am?
I am the Great Hina Chono.
"I am The Great Hina Chono"
You know?
Really?
"I am The Great Hina Chono"
You know?
Really?
"I am The Great Hina Chono"
You know?
I am nervous.
This is completely different from when I'm doing gymnastics in front of an audience.
And I didn't expect to be paired up with you, Taiki.
But...
I know everyone's counting on me as the lead.
And I've been rehearsing as best as I can.
Right.
So...
Right now, as one of my closest friends, help me out with everything you've got!
Don't worry.
It's less embarrassing than
the Sports Day in our 2nd year of Junior High.
I wasn't the one who picked that!
Still, it was rough!
But we all performed it together.
How about what you did during our 3rd year of Junior High?
I pulled that off flawlessly.
Good work, everyone.
That's what they say.
Huh?
Really?
What're you guys talking about?
We're wondering if those two are dating.
They've always been so close.
I think they're just friends.
Really? You serious?
But surely, what exactly is the difference between a platonic friend and a lover?
I wonder what it is.
1-B presents "Snow White"
The act begins.
Once upon a time...
there was a queen...
who gave birth to a beautiful girl.
The baby's skin was as white as snow.
So her mother named her "Snow White".
Ah...
Snow White was bright and lively.
I can see how she's the chosen one of the rhythmic gymnastics team.
Every day, she frolicked through the forest...
She's got this aura about her.
until her cheeks glowed as red as apples.
It's like she was made for the stage.
What... are you doing here?
It's pretty obvious that he's nervous.
He's moving like a robot.
But you can tell he's trying his best.
Hm? Wait a second.
I don't remember Snow White having a scene like this.
Apparently, they took some liberties with it.
Somebody made the argument that it wasn't reasonable to have her marry some guy...
who'd popped out of nowhere.
So they added a scene at the beginning where she meets the prince.
And that's when Snow White falls in love with him.
So at the end, the kiss that wakes her up comes from the man she loves.
That was a great rewrite.
I wouldn't...
want to wake up being kissed by someone I don't know.
It's nice when you can marry the person you've always loved.
What?
I think it's worse that way.
Idealizing that kind of long-standing love...
is, like, way too heavy.
Isn't it more fun to enjoy a light-hearted love affair?
You're way too wild, Ayame.
It's everyone else who's too uptight.
Now help us out.
Beautiful young lady, let me give you a gift.
That's a beautiful apple.
That apple is so red and shiny, with a deep indent at the bottom.
Right, right.
The sugar content of this apple seems to be over 15 degrees!
The play's halfway over.
Wow, Taiki's seriously frantic over the kiss scene.
It is the highlight of the play.
Oh, by the way, remember what you asked about earlier?
Ah, you see, the difference between platonic friends and lovers...
Oh, right. That.
I remember something my older brother said.
Simply the matter...
whether you can kiss that person or not.
K i s s ?
Kiss?
Keep your voice down.
Oops. Do you think the audience can hear us?
Yeah, that too.
Granted, this is just the opinion of my free-spirited brother.
But he says crossing the line of friendship...
depends on whether or not you want to touch them.
By that logic...
Taiki is...
Huh?
Whatcha guys talking about?
Don't tell him.
Huh? Am I being left out?
Right now, I need to focus on the play right now!
Oh.. my goodness, Snow White...
I can't believe she's really dead.
Hina's counting on me...
as one of her closest friends.
Ah.
Prince!
What's with you going in for the kill while I was asleep?
Huh?
Apparently they added that too.
So aggressive.
Oh, good.
We're almost done here.
Now for the ending...
Huh?!
Hina, watch out!
Are you okay?!
Are any of you hurt?
Our apologies, but the play will be temporarily put on hold.
Wait, you mean they actually kissed?
You sure you're not imagining things?
Don't think about that.
You should be more concerned about their welfare!
Chono and I think the boy was from the badminton team...
They're together a lot.
Aren't they dating?
What? No way.
I told you! Our lips didn't touch!
Maybe it looked that way because of all the confetti...
but I stopped myself before that happened.
Really?
Aren't you just embarrassed and trying to cover it up?
Just tell us the truth.
It is the truth!
Is it, Chono-san?
Yes.
Oh, really?
Still, everyone's talking about it.
People are wondering if you two are dating.
After all, you're the princess and prince!
Even if you didn't kiss, everyone's still gonna talk.
You guys had great chemistry on stage.
Anyone who was watching is going to believe the rumors, you know?
It's true...
that it may have looked like we kissed.
But I don't appreciate you making fun of me like this. So please stop it.
Ah... sorry.
I get wanting to gossip about it.
But who I go out with is none of their business.
Taiki!
I'm sorry that stupid rumor's going around.
It's not your fault.
And I'm the one who's sorry.
I couldn't make the play a success.
That's not true!
You remembered more of your lines than I expected!
At first you were nervous, but you got better and better.
You carried yourself with pride and projected your voice.
And...
And!
You weren't overshadowed by my limelight!
Consider that a compliment!
Okay, in exchange, you can reward me by doing my homework.
Sure, if you don't mind a bunch of errors.
Then what's the point?
But, if I must...
I can explain to Chinatsu-senpai that we didn't kiss. Just say the word!
Eh.
I know you wouldn't like her getting the wrong idea.
That's why you got so mad.
And I want a fair fight!
No, that's...
That's not it.
Let's have a mini celebration.
You must be all sorts of tired.
Kyo...
No need to inhale it.
Let me enjoy this!
All anyone wants to talk about is the kiss!
kiss!
I wish they'd compliment the play first!
I did pretty good for a pinch hitter!
You did.
Why'd that darn confetti ball have to fall?
What would they do if we got injured?
It's rare for him to be in such a bad mood.
Even Hina!
She thinks I'm upset about Chinatsu-senpai!
You aren't?
Sure, there's that too.
But I'm more upset over how people are talking about us.
My current relationship with Hina is unclear.
I have to be careful with every move I make.
I hate all these rumors going around.
I figured Hina felt the same way.
Granted, I'm the one choosing to get mad about this.
I want to ask you something.
What is it?
Don't you feel anything romantic toward Chono?
Huh?
With how hard she's come onto you, I wouldn't blame you if you did.
The one I like is...
Chinatsu-senpai.
Right.
No, I mean...
it feels like you're putting 100% into Chinatsu-senpai...
but I think there could be...
an additional 30% of feelings for Chono on top of that.
I could imagine that.
This is all just hypothetical.
Ah...
My head hurts...
No matter how much it hurts, you need to think about it.
Yeah.
Thank you for coming today.
So, that was a girl.
Then I still have a chance.
We're leaving.
I wonder if people from Kansai eat...
takoyaki and rice together?
That's the guy. The one they say kissed her.
As of now...
Hmm...
The 53rd Annual Eimei Culture Festival has concluded...
100% coffee...
30% milk...
Yummy.
So it's possible...
to have feelings for both of them.
Ah...
Wait, stop that!!
Ishiki
Milk
100% RAW Milk
Keep Cool
This is Kyo's fault for saying all that weird stuff.
I like Chinatsu-senpai.
Ch-Chinatsu senpai? What are you doing here?!
My grandpa's surgery was a success.
I'm moving back in the day after tomorrow.
I came to drop off my stuff.
Right, she'd said it'd be any day now.
Thanks for having me again.
The pleasure's all mine.
Chinatsu-senpai saw that too.
I wonder what she thought about it.
The evening breeze, like it’s cooling down my flushed cheeks
Is gentle
The day I walked beside you will become something that lasts a lifetime
I know you’re being kind without thinking much of it
shii
But still, I can feel it clearly
Tte
chan
Ah, my focus jumps up
shuu
chuu
ryo
ku
With just one word, it gets hot
A tiny sign
Hon
no
chii
I end up dreaming
Why am I so happy?
shii
no
Why am I so sad?
shii
no
Even now, I gaze at you beside me
Your distant profile burned into my memory, ah
Today, I still can’t reach you
Though you’re so close
Brought to you by [KawaSubs]