Do you know about the campfire jinx?
The one that says you'll be lovey-dovey if you confess?
Yeah. That really iffy one.
Iffy...
Since we're all here, why don't you try it out?
Ask him for his answer to your confession.
I won't.
Until Taiki falls for me too...
I don't need an answer.
I brought it.
Thank you.
Huh!
Should I just throw it away?
The feelings rolling around in my frozen hands
Don’t give up! Wish like you’re dancing
“There’s still time”
With a barefoot heart, I run forward
Blue    Box
I couldn’t say it—how I wanted things to stay like this just a little longer
I’m tired of pretending to be a fool, so maybe I’ll just quit
It’s probably an unrequited love, right? Truly a pathetic kind of love
It’s already too big to turn into a lie
Once again, I realize I love you, and it hurts
Maybe it’s a love that can’t be helped But it’s not a bad kind of love
shi,
I want to chase after your way of living, your dreams
I want to watch you
Mi
te
i
ta
Episode 24: A Roller Coaster
Last night...
I'm glad that old lady was safe.
Yeah, me too.
It's getting late...
I knew it from the start.
While knowing that he likes Chinatsu-senpai,
I confessed my feelings.
Hina!
So this isn't a problem at all!
I'll carry this.
Thanks.
Besides there's more to this than pain.
When I told him how I feel...
I got a real kick out of seeing his slack-jawed reaction.
As part of Operation: Make Taiki Look At Me...
When I say something to make Taiki turn red...
I feel such a rush.
These mini Hinas in my head do a little dance.
When we worked on Snow White for the Culture Festival...
Snow
White
Performance Script
"Wake up..."
(The prince kisses her)
I would fantasize about Taiki playing
the role of the prince.
"Wake up..."
(The prince kisses her)
Heh.. heh...
When that fantasy became real...
I was ridiculously nervous.
I saw a sight...
that I will never forget.
Taiki probably has no idea...
Back then...
I imagined I really did share a kiss with you, Taiki.
Huh?!
Wanna do it for real?
I'd really wished he'd done it.
In that quiet classroom...
my body was tingling with a feverish hum...
and my heart was pounding so hard it hurt.
Hina, watch out!
Huh?!
At that time...
I didn't want my first kiss to be up on a stage,
so I'm glad it worked out the way it did.
And then there's the way everyone started talking about it.
Apparently, Taiki was standing up for me, but...
it's not like I was totally unhappy with the gossip.
What if...
he'd go out with me for real.
I wondered...
what it'd be like if we really did date.
How would it feel like?
Walking home with him or going to karaoke...
I'd want to take a ton of photos.
And hold hands...
Huh!
Hmm...
Ah...
Is this how it feels like to have a roller coaster of emotions...
He should try going out with me...
Even if it's just for fun.
I sometimes think all that.
But I like his sense of integrity too.
He's just that kind of person.
If I told him that, then he wouldn't so flippantly hurt me.
The meat's not ready yet...
I'm not that much of a glutton!
Ah.
You've got a leaf in your hair.
Ah, where?
Higher.
Huh?
More back.
Back?
Sorry. I'm gonna touch your hair.
It's getting more stuck.
I like you.
But if I said that right now, it'd only stress him out, wouldn't it?
But...
Got it.
you miss every shot you don't take,
so I'm going to make the most of this relationship.
Look at me.
I want you to be more than a good friend.
Maybe tomorrow.
Maybe next week.
Maybe next month.
I'll wait forever.
So for now...
You've got one right there too.
You're just gonna stick it in my hair!
No, I'm not!
Look, there's a big bug here.
Eh, where?!
Just kidding.
Oh, my. Someone's getting closer.
I envy those kind of couples who are like friends.
You seem like the type to toy around with your partners, Moriya-san.
That's not true though.
But even if I did...
I go out with people who'd be okay with that.
When it comes to love...
the person who's being doted on is the happiest.
Then how does the other person find happiness?
Huh?
Moriya-san...
Even if you go out with someone, it doesn't last that long, right?
Not to be rude, but...
So what do you even know?
Huh?
WHAT?!
Why's this four-eyes butting into my business?!
You don't even have a girlfriend!
He pisses me off!
Good job at the training camp, everyone!
Let's light it up!
Nyeh!
Tch!
So what do you even know?
It's true I've never been in a long-term relationship...
much less felt anything that could be called true love.
However!
Because I enjoy loving Taiki...
That's why!
I want to cheer on...
people who are madly in love!
Ah.
It's cold...
Don't you have a jacket?
Yeah, but I left it in the gym.
I'll go get it.
Hinachi! Hinachi!
Seems the sound equipment's acting up.
There should be extra in the gym, so would you fetch it for me?
Sure!
Really? Thanks.
And for the record...
you can take as long as you need getting back.
Huh?
Ah.
What's up?
I came to grab some equipment.
Ayame-chan asked me to.
That manager loves ordering people around.
Ah.
I'LL...
...HELP
YOU!
I'll help you.
YOU
CAN
TAKE...
YOU
CAN
TAKE...
...AS
LONG
AS YOU
NEED!
...AS
LONG
AS YOU
NEED!
You can take as long as you need!
She did this on purpose.
What equipment do you need?
I'll help you out.
I don't see it.
Hmm...
I bet Ayame-chan just made that up.
Ah.
You can see the campfire from here too.
Huh, that's true.
It looks even more otherworldly.
Ah, Nishida-senpai's dancing!
Let's watch it from here for a while!
Good idea. I am pretty tired.
I wouldn't mind a breather.
I'm surprised that even you'd get tired seeing how you exercise year-round.
You're making fun of me, huh.
I burn far more energy than
some young lady who travels by bus.
We did morning sprints too!
That reminds me!
Hotel in the Mountains
Our school trip in our third year of middle school...
you'd sneak out of the hotel in the morning...
to go running.
Cuz it's part of my daily routine.
But you got in so much trouble.
The teacher only found out cuz everyone teased me about it.
Oh! And then when we went camping our second year and we played cops and robbers...
HYUCK
Oh, yeah. I was the only one who got away.
SHADOW CLONES
You sure showed off some fancy footwork, Taiki.
What a hoot.
That's not a compliment.
Well, I was watching you too.
You got caught first and looked so bored for the rest of the game.
It was my shoelaces!
Yeah. Excuses.
They say the wise hawk hides her talons!
Sure, but even during the second round,
you still got caught first.
You never even realized when you were freed.
Huh?
Hey, Taiki.
Hm?
I have a question.
What is it?
When we were playing King's game...
Hmm...
What were you really going to answer with?
For a second there...
I thought you were going to tell everyone how you like Chinatsu-senpai!
But you're more of a scaredy-cat than I thought.
I guess you're not so impulsive that you'd spill your feelings for someone during a game.
Ah! I mean, you could if you wanted to.
That was my promise from the start.
I'd be totally fine.
I just gotta work harder than you.
But to be honest, it sometimes stings.
Still, I don't mind that sorta stuff...
because I love you so much!
Let's start heading back!
I have to tell Ayame-chan it wasn't there!
Oh, geez. I didn't mean to say that I like him here.
Hina.
Hm?
Sorry.
Sorry? About what?
I can't go out with you.
Stop.
I told you I didn't need a reply.
Don't rush it.
It's not like you're going out with Chinatsu-senpai, right?
Well... No.
Then you don't have to give me an answer yet.
No matter how long it takes, I won't complain.
If you reject me now...
you might regret it when you end up liking me later.
Even so...
I don't think the relationship we have right now is healthy.
You said it's okay for me to try to get closer to Chinatsu-senpai, but...
the way things stand, I really can't face her in good faith.
I like her, but...
I feel awful for how I'm swayed by you.
I think my indecisiveness is only going to hurt you, Hina.
So let me draw the line here.
Both of us—
I said it's fine!
I told you how I feel, knowing full well you liked somebody else.
Even if you like her...
I still like you!
That's not normal.
It is normal!
If I can get you to look my way, it'll all come full circle.
I can't reciprocate your feelings.
Why not?!
I'm the one...
who has tons of memories with you!
Is it because we don't live together?
Then we could start now!
I don't know how Chinatsu-senpai feels about you, but...
I—
Even then...
It won't change who I like.
Hina!
Hehe~ I wonder if it worked out.
Just the two of them, alone in a gym lit by the glow of the campfire...
Apparently, there's some jinx about it.
They gotta be suckered by the romantic atmosphere.
Ah.
Huh!
Hinachi!
Are you okay?
Did someth—
Ah.
She's crying.
He said he can't go out with me...
because he likes someone else.
Even though they don't like each other the same way...
it doesn't change who he likes.
If this were rhythmic gymnastics...
I'd be told that my efforts will be rewarded.
People would say all sorts of things.
But I worked hard and have the results to show for it.
The harder I worked, the more I liked myself.
But...
When it comes to love...
Huh?
Why am I so pathetic?
The evening breeze, like it’s cooling down my flushed cheeks
Is gentle
The day I walked beside you will become something that lasts a lifetime
I know you’re being kind without thinking much of it
shii
But still, I can feel it clearly
Tte
chan
Ah, my focus jumps up
shuu
chuu
ryo
ku
With just one word, it gets hot
A tiny sign
Hon
no
chii
I end up dreaming
Why am I so happy?
shii
no
Why am I so sad?
shii
no
Even now, I gaze at you beside me
Your distant profile burned into my memory, ah
Today, I still can’t reach you
Though you’re so close
Brought to you by [KawaSubs]