Ah, this is Kyo's fault for saying all that weird stuff.
I like Chinatsu-senpai...
Ch-Chinatsu senpai? What are you doing here?!
My grandpa's surgery was a success.
I'm moving back in the day after tomorrow.
I came to drop off my stuff.
Right, she'd said it'd be any day now.
Thanks for having me again.
The pleasure's all mine.
Yup! I'm sleeping over at Karen's tonight.
You two sure are close.
Well, we've been friends since kindergarten.
She's acting totally normal.
Does she not have any thoughts on the play?
Maybe she didn't actually watch it.
But I think...
she'd just tell me if she couldn't make it.
Oh, what a royal mess this is!
On the way back from shopping, we were enjoying some popcorn...
when Chi's mom spilled the whole bag right outside the front door!
Ah, where are those garbage bags...
I'll help clean up.
Sorry for bothering.
Chinatsu-senpai!
Huh?
About the Cultural Festival play...
Yummy, right?
That's not the issue here!
What about the rumors...
that Hina and I kissed or that we're going out?
Even if Chinatsu-senpai doesn't mind...
I want to talk about it!
Should I just throw it away?
The feelings rolling around in my frozen hands
Don’t give up! Wish like you’re dancing
“There’s still time”
With a barefoot heart, I run forward
Blue    Box
I couldn’t say it—how I wanted things to stay like this just a little longer
I’m tired of pretending to be a fool, so maybe I’ll just quit
It’s probably an unrequited love, right? Truly a pathetic kind of love
It’s already too big to turn into a lie
Once again, I realize I love you, and it hurts
Maybe it’s a love that can’t be helped But it’s not a bad kind of love
shi,
I want to chase after your way of living, your dreams
I want to watch you
Mi
te
i
ta
Episode 21: A Chance to Blossom
Taiki, I'm here to lend an ear!
Huh?
No worries! I understand completely.
I know that you didn't kiss.
And that the rumor about you going out is a lie.
It is all a lie, right?
Yes, but please back off...
Don't betray me like Haryu did...
Nishida's secret crush went to
his fortune-telling booth and...
wanted advice about her crush on a track team member.
I'm just glad you didn't get hurt or anything.
I almost had a heart attack when that confetti ball fell.
You saw the play?
As the team captain, of course I did.
I was with Haryu and his girlfriend, plus Kano from the girls basketball team.
Ah.
So Chinatsu-senpai did see it!
Even the second and third-year students are talking about it.
Can you blame them?
That rhythmic gymnastics girl is famous.
Anyone who witnessed it knew it was an accident...
but rumors like that have a tendency to get around.
Make sure you protect her.
Huh.
That'll cost ya 4,000 yen.
You've raised the price?!
No.
That's for two.
Me too?!
Just kidding!
Hina!
Coming!
Yeah, no way she'd go out with you.
If I catch anyone talkin' crap...
I'll give 'em something to talk about!
Thanks!
It's those two, right?
People said they're dating.
I heard it isn't true.
What? Really?
Are you okay with all these weird rumors going around?
You're moving back in, right?
Ah...
Did you see that?! I shot it just like Curry!
But she's only living there,
so she can keep playing basketball.
Once more.
I guess Chinatsu's not interested in this sort of stuff.
Still, it's been ages...
since you last slept over at my place.
You came over all the time when we were little.
That's because I've my sports club activities.
Everyone's always like "club" this or "club" that.
You've got work though, don't you?
Yeah, but...
It sounds like Kengo will be busy with practice for a while too.
He can feel so standoffish at times like this.
He won't contact me as often.
You say that, but...
don't you still get mad whenever he prioritizes you over practice?
Well, naturally!
I don't like being his excuse for anything.
Besides...
he looks the coolest
when he's playing badminton...
Just cannot help it.
I'll just get my much-needed attention from you, Chi.
You've got it too good.
Two-timing, hehe.
Okay, I gotta make sure to shoo away the flies who aren't on your level.
Flies?
Flies
I'm only saying this because someone asked me to.
So, one of my friends from another school wants to get to know you.
He wants me to get your number for him.
No thanks.
That was fast.
Well, I'm not good at talking to people I don't even know.
You really aren't interested in romance, huh?
I wanna marry you, Sensei!
Me too!
Remember Nakamura-sensei back in kindergarten?
Only you were totally uninterested.
Cuz everyone was acting too mature!
But it's true that I was never as good as other kids with that sorta stuff.
Could it be that there's already someone you're interested in?
Why does she look so troubled?
Yes, there is someone...
I'm interested in.
Is that someone perhaps...
Inomata-kun?
Yeah.
So you like him.
No, I wouldn't say that yet.
Huh? Ah... not yet?
Wouldn't say that yet?
Hmm... how should I put it?
It's like growing a flower.
Again with the quirky analogies.
My interest in him is like a little seedling popping out of the dirt.
When I used to see him at morning practice...
I'd only think "That kid's here a lot".
But as we started talking and I got to know him...
my thoughts shifted to "He's a nice guy"...
and the bud sprouted.
Every time I think about how nice he is...
that plant grows bigger and bigger.
But I'm so focused on basketball...
and my current circumstances...
that it hasn't had a chance to blossom yet.
So if this flower blossoms, then she likes him.
But then what happened during the play...
that rattled me.
Well, I'm not one to fall for people that easily either.
So I get how you feel.
But all that stuff about whether they kissed or not...
It doesn't matter that it was an accident.
The moment those kinds of rumors spread, it's all just nonsense.
I'm saying, if it were me, it'd be over.
But when you look at different people...
that moment when the bud sprouted as you put it, some would call that love.
It's different for everyone. I'm not saying
one is right and the other way is wrong.
I think how fast someone falls in love comes down to who they are.
You're not the type who wants a boyfriend and decides to fall in love.
I believe you're very cautious when it comes to love.
so I understand how you still don't feel that
you can say you like Inomata-kun.
But...
while you're busy saying that...
someone could swoop in and snatch him away.
That's not a nice thing to say...
It's reality.
What I'm trying to say is...
I want you to have a wonderful love.
I might not know when it'll happen...
but if ever the time comes when you feel you love someone...
I want you to acknowledge that feeling.
Hmm.
For some people...
that sprouting bud would already mean they like the person.
But I'm sure something is missing for Chinatsu to feel the same way.
I wish my little sister could take
a page out of your book.
Why?
She's such a serial monogamist, always dating around.
She said she dumped her last boyfriend
because he walked too fast.
Sis~
Can I borrow your nail polish remover?
Speak of the devil.
I already gave it to you before, Ayame.
Huh? I don't have it...
Aw! It's Chi-chan!
Your hair's as silky as ever and you have such pretty skin!
It really must be all that exercise.
You hate exercise.
I hate getting sweaty.
By the way, didn't you have a date
with your boyfriend today?
I broke up with him.
Again?!
Well, everytime we went to a cafe...
the barista couldn't get whether he was ordering a M or L...
I mean, he should speak more clearly.
But it's okay!
I've found another guy to pine over!
Chi. Do not use this girl as a reference.
What're you talking about?
About how you're so footloose and fancy-free.
By the way, what do you like about this guy?
Huh? His face!
Inomata
Starting today, I'm in your care again.
Welcome home!
How I've missed you!
I feel like you're my own child already!
Ah, come on in.
I'll bring in your luggage.
Let's have sushi like we did on her first day!
Here we go! Personal belongings, coming through!
I'll carry those.
Oh?
As always, I have no clue what she's thinking.
Taiki.
They'd like you to give these club funds to the seniors.
Thank you.
Did your net break?
You mean the strings?
Wow. You dare laugh at the ignorant?
You fool.
I didn't laugh!
As expected, those two...
That rumor was true after all.
Don't let them get to you.
I've thought up a way to work the rumors in my favor.
In your favor?
"It's up to Taiki to make it a reality
whenever he wants."
What?!
It worked! It worked!
Looks like it's problem solved for me!
I'll go with that strategy for a while!
What was I ever worried about?
Ah...
Granted, that's just Hina's way
of being considerate.
Don't say anything!
I wasn't gonna.
Gather round!
Okay!
Ah, I believe each of you...
set your own goals at the beginning of this term.
I have to think about so many things.
Since the Culture Festival's over...
I have to focus on badminton again.
I'll need to improve if I hope to beat Yusa again.
Starting today, we have a new member.
She's not a player.
Hello!
I'm your new team manager, Ayame Moriya.
Cu-Cute...
We finally have our very own girl manager!
Yay!
Welcome!
Oh? Where's the kid with the bowl cut?
Huh?
I saw him in the gym two weeks back.
Hottie Alert! Totally my type!
HOTTIE
ALERT!
Totally
my type!!
HOTTIE
ALERT!
This aloof, scrawny, macho kid with a bowl cut...
HOTTIE
ALERT!
I think you're talking about Yusa.
He attends Sajikawa High School.
He only came for a practice meet.
Oh, then I won't get to see him every day?
He goes to another school.
And I won't get to wash his track suit?
You want to do that?
Well, it's been nice knowing you..
Wait!
Kengo.
Karen was right.
You suddenly volunterring for a manager meant there's something behind it...
But...
His face was totally in my type!
I want to see that cool and aloof face get all flustered!
Haryu, you know her?
She's my girlfriend's little sister.
Karen-san's lil sis?
But we'll probably have another practice match with them...
and you can see him at tournaments.
Actually, that's probably the only way you'd run into him.
Fine. I guess we can work together for a little while.
This girl's really got her own agenda.
Okay, Taiki. Tell her about her duties.
Okay!
This is the storeroom.
Here, we prepare the team cooler.
And this is...
the locker room.
Ah...
It's a little messy at the moment.
"A little"? Does nobody clean up?
It reeks!
I seriously don't believe this.
This girl has zero filter.
She's Karen's little sister and
doesn't seem like a bad person, but...
Huh!
Aaah! Spider spider spider spider!
A lil too close...
Hmm..
Chi-chan, save me!
It sounds like I did something!
Spider...
Inomata-kun, what did you do?
I didn't do anything! It was just a spider...
Aah!
Aaah! It's coming for me again!
Chase it out of here!
Don't push me! I'll find a tissue or something.
Just pick it up with your bare hands!
But...
As expected from Chi-chan!
Huh? I thought Chinatsu-senpai hated bugs.
I have the power to fight.
I guess she overcame her fear.
So, what's Ayame-chan doing in the boys' badminton locker room?
I somehow ended up being their manager.
You volunteered for the job.
Manager...
This guy's explaining me my duties.
"This guy"?
What's your name again?
Taiki Inomata.
Then it's "Inota".
Huh?
Let's go, inota! We've gotta get garbage bags and clean this place up.
Don't call me like I'm some pet.
Well, see you later, Chi-chan!
Ah...
We'll need rubber gloves too.
..how fast someone falls in love comes down to who they are.
Is this what she meant?
It's so heavy!
Heave ho.
That's the girl who became the badminton team's manager.
It's so hot!
Huh!
How everyone can move around so much in this heat.
Here I go!
I can't win...
Where are you fighting?
I've got the cooler ready!
Thanks!
Thank you, manager!
Oh, back to life!
Inota, what's next?
I'll teach you how to keep score.
Oh, lemme see!
This is hard for me to say, but...
Huh?
maybe you are too close.
We wouldn't want to start any strange rumors.
So you should keep your distance.
Rumours?
The guy who played the prince in Snow White!
You realized that now?
My friend told me about it. It must be hard hearing all that chatter about you.
You know, about whether or not you two kissed.
Everybody makes way too big a deal over some little kiss.
"some little kiss"?
Anyway, you shouldn't worry about it.
Other than worrying about the opinions of those who actually care about you...
just ignore what people say.
Be that as it may. Could you give me a little space?
Sorry, sorry.
It's a habit... huh?
Ah.
Spiderr!
Hey! I just told you...
Uuuuuh!
Oh, is that so?
Ah!
Quick, Inota!
Oh, I forgot something.
Aaaaah!
It's not what you think!!!
The evening breeze, like it’s cooling down my flushed cheeks
Is gentle
The day I walked beside you will become something that lasts a lifetime
I know you’re being kind without thinking much of it
shii
But still, I can feel it clearly
Tte
chan
Ah, my focus jumps up
shuu
chuu
ryo
ku
With just one word, it gets hot
A tiny sign
Hon
no
chii
I end up dreaming
Why am I so happy?
shii
no
Why am I so sad?
shii
no
Even now, I gaze at you beside me
Your distant profile burned into my memory, ah
Today, I still can’t reach you
Though you’re so close
Brought to you by [KawaSubs]