Inter-High's over...
and the vacation's almost over.
It's that time when students rush to get their homework done.
Today is August 26.
Chinatsu!
Happy Birthday!
Thanks!
All right. All right.
Put this on.
Here's a gift for you.
Ohh, what is it?
It's a deer T-shirt by the artist Chinatsu!
Cheese!
Yay!
Should I just throw it away?
The feelings rolling around in my frozen hands
Don’t give up! Wish like you’re dancing
“There’s still time”
With a barefoot heart, I run forward
Blue    Box
I couldn’t say it—how I wanted things to stay like this just a little longer
I’m tired of pretending to be a fool, so maybe I’ll just quit
It’s probably an unrequited love, right? Truly a pathetic kind of love
It’s already too big to turn into a lie
Once again, I realize I love you, and it hurts
Maybe it’s a love that can’t be helped But it’s not a bad kind of love
shi,
I want to chase after your way of living, your dreams
I want to watch you
Mi
te
i
ta
Episode 15: August 26
Eh, that's good.
Girls sure love that sorta stuff.
It's blinding.
Seems like it's her birthday.
I know.
For the past few weeks...
I've been gathering intel and contemplating the perfect gift.
but I kept thinking of gifts that would come off as too serious...
Well, it's tough picking out the right birthday present.
Plus...
Ever since the Inter-High ended, Chinatsu-senpai's seemed sorta down.
so it doesn't feel right to celebrate.
But maybe I can come up with something by tonight—
Ouch!
Oh.
Sorry about that.
You did that on purpose.
How rude!
It's not like I'm making up an excuse to talk to you.
Hina. We need to talk. Is now good?
Huh?
What is it?
Something weird perhaps?
That's not funny and don't play dumb!
Just trying to lighten the mood.
Hina, listen.
You said you didn't need me to respond right away, right?
Yeah.
But the truth is I like Chinatsu-senpai.
I'm going to do everything I can to make that work, is that okay?
Huh? Sure.
I told you.
I already know you like Senpai.
It's more awkward when you act all stiff around me!
That can't be good.
Chinatsu!
What are you doing? The defense is closing in on you.
Try passing to the opposite side too!
Okay!
The coach sure is hard on Chinatsu.
It can't be helped.
Our best senior players are gone now.
It may not be fair to chinatsu, but...
in the end, he needs her to be the one who can nail a clutch shot.
What'd the coach say?
Since Yoshitani-senpai left the team, he told me to try my best as vice-captain.
Thought so!
Chinatsu's sure to be the captain next semester.
That's perfect. She's the best player...
and all the younger players trust her!
But will you be okay?
Leading isn't really your forte, is it?
I may seem false, but I was the class representative last semester!
AHEM!
Only because you lost at rock-paper-scissors.
It's true that it's a lot of pressure...
But I love this team.
Well said!
We've got your back, Vice-Captain!
So cool!
Hey!
I'm locking up soon.
Okay!
Mom
Hello.
CHINATSU! HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
Mom... you startled me.
I had to make sure my voice reached you all the way over in Japan.
So? Anything new?
Nope, nothing.
Really? You sound a little down.
The phone always makes me sound like that.
Is that so?
It's not a big deal, but...
Huh?
The coach made me Vice-captain of the team.
That's amazing!
Since I was chosen for the position, I need to try my best.
I think...
I already told you, but...
I missed the shot when it is really mattered.
I'd practiced so hard.
But I still missed.
Just talking about basketball...
I have so much growing up to do.
How will I even have the time to think about the team?
I wonder if I'm actually good enough...
Oh, Chinatsu.
Save your worries for when you try it and it doesn't work...
And even then, it still won't be too late to improve.
And when the time comes...
don't think that you failed because of who you are.
Think about how you can grow from your experiences.
Going forward, you should be focusing on...
who you can turn to...
when the going gets tough.
Ah...
It's pretty nice, you know?
When someone relies on you...
Oh, I need to hang up soon.
Okay, thanks.
Ah...
Huh?
Hmm?
I wasn't following you.
I just happened to be...
Anyway... I see you sent this.
I thought she wouldn't send it anymore.
I want to go somewhere.
Do you mind if we take the train?
We'll be there soon.
Hmm.
Huh!
The sea!
I used to come here a lot when I was in elementary school.
But it's too late to go in the water now...
So she does have a childish side.
Thank goodness.
She looks a little happier.
Taiki-kun, come here!
Hang on.
Come on. Hurry up!
Huh?
Senpai.. your wish ribbon...
Oh, that's right. It fell off.
I knew it. We overloaded with too many wishes.
Sorry.
I see...
Now we don't have a matching pair anymore.
What'd you do that for?
Because you were spacing out.
One more!
Quit it!
Wait, wait!
Here I go.
Whoa, it's cold!
There're really still kids acting like this, huh?
They're as dazzling as the midsummer sun.
It looks like the weather's turning foul.
Chinatsu-senpai! Time out! Wait a min!
The sand gives way around here.
Really?
It's true, you need to be careful...
Thanks.
Yeah.
Eh?
I wouldn't want to trip and get all wet.
Ah, right.
It's a good thing you brought your club jersey.
Do I look like a local?
I have to ride the train like this?
No way your pants will dry in time.
Let's head home once the sun sets.
Thanks for bringing me here.
Chinatsu-senpai! Today's your birthday, right?
Yeah.
I don't know if this counts as a present, but...
I got you this little thing.
A cake!
You brought this with you?
I asked for a bunch of ice packs to keep it cool.
There're candles too.
Whoa, I am already 17.
Birthdays are significant.
You can feel yourself getting closer to adulthood.
Your birthday's in January, right, Taiki?
Yeah. January 15.
Right now, you're 15 years old.
So we're two years apart.
Two years isn't that big gap.
That's right.
We're still kids until we come of age!
Okay! Now let's sing!
We're gonna sing?
Happy.. Birth.. day..
to you.
Happy Birthday... to you...
Happy Birthday dear...
Chinatsu-senpai...
Happy Birthday to you.
The wind blow them out.
Want me to relight them?
It's fine.
Now let's eat.
Also about the wish ribbon...
We'll have a matching pair again.
Next year, when mine comes off too.
What's so funny?
Hmm, it's nothing.
Hey! It's definitely something!
I was just thinking how pretentious you can be, Taiki.
What?!
This way.
That downpour came out of nowhere.
We still ended up soaked.
When we get home, my mother gonna scold me.
NOTICE
THIS TRAIN IS
SUSPENDED
DUE TO A LANDSLIDE,
UNTIL REPAIRS ARE
COMPLETED.
Eh?
NOTICE
THIS TRAIN IS
SUSPENDED
DUE TO A LANDSLIDE
Ah...
Ehh!
I know. I said I'm sorry.
We were at the beach, and there was a landslide.
Uh-oh. They happened to only have one room available.
We'll be fine. The whole gang's here.
Okay. See you.
What the heck is fine about this?!
We can't go home because of a landslide.
The inn we ran to only had one room available.
And I lied to my parents and told them that everyone's here.
For one night, I'll be sharing a room with Chinatsu-senpai.
Not that I'll do anything inappropriate.
I hope that she's not disappointed...
something like this happened on her birthday.
Are you done with your phone call?
What did Yukiko-san say?
Oh.. She just told us to be careful.
I see.
I knew it. This is bad!
There's no way I'll be able to sleep like this.
Taiki-kun.
These were in the lobby!
Let's play some together!
As we're having a sleepover, let's spend the night having a board game blitz!
What would you like?
Sure. Anything for the birthday girl.
Yep! It is my birthday!
She's fast.
I'll deal.
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
Oh, I'm getting a call from Nagisa.
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
ANSWER
REJECT
NAGISA
Incoming video call...
Sorry, can I take this?
Sure. Want me to leave?
Nah, it's fine.
Oh.
It's a video call.
Huh?
Happy Birthday Part 2!
Thanks!
Huh? Maybe it wasn't necessary to hide like this.
You called to celebrate?
I also wanted...
to tell you something, Chinatsu.
Today, well lately...
you've seemed down.
I know there's a lot of pressure on you, but I'm here to support you, Chinatsu.
I'm confident we're gonna do even better than before.
So, let's stronger as a team!
Yeah.
Thanks.
I just wanted you to hear that.
But, you know, you already look more relaxed.
Eh.
During practice, you seemed way more stressed.
I can't stay down forever.
Okay. Okay.
But wait, what? You're wearing a yukata!
Are you at an inn?
Yeah. I'm here with the family I'm staying with.
Oh, I see. You look like you're enjoying yourself.
You were disappointed that you couldn't wear a yukata during the fireworks festival.
That's not true.
Oh, come on.You were so jealous over everybody else's outfits.
So were you, Nagisa.
I'm glad I could see Chinatsu-senpai in a yukata.
Well, I'd better let you go.
Hmm.
Ah!
Nice catch!
Just now, I let out a yell...
It's fine. I'm pretty sure I already hung up.
Did I hear a guy's voice just now?
Maybe it's the uncle?
That's a relief.
You have really good friends.
Right?
I'm only surrounded by good people.
Actually, about the fireworks festival...
I have something I want to apologize for, Chinatsu-senpai.
Huh?
When I was telling about it at home...
I said I was going in a group.
But in the end, I couldn't get everyone together...
and Kyo got a fever the day of.
So I didn't go with everyone.
That made it seem like I was lying to you on purpose.
And I'm sorry about that.
You don't have to apologise for that.
Maybe, that's true. But...
I still wanted to apologise for that.
Then I also have something I hope you'll forgive me for.
What is it?
I want to take back what I said...
about it not being good.
I'm the one who drew boundaries and made you keep your distance.
I realize it was rude to do that to you.
What? No...
I get how Chinatsu-senpai was feeling.
And...
That is why...
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize for that.
Then that makes us even.
Okay, let's play cards!
Since there's two of us, how about One-card?
Never played it before...
Really?!
Hmm?
Ah...
Why didn't he sleep in his futon?
He's going to be sore.
Hmm...
Good morning...
to the 17-year-old me.
The evening breeze, like it’s cooling down my flushed cheeks
Is gentle
The day I walked beside you will become something that lasts a lifetime
I know you’re being kind without thinking much of it
shii
But still, I can feel it clearly
Tte
chan
Ah, my focus jumps up
shuu
chuu
ryo
ku
With just one word, it gets hot
A tiny sign
Hon
no
chii
I end up dreaming
Why am I so happy?
shii
no
Why am I so sad?
shii
no
Even now, I gaze at you beside me
Your distant profile burned into my memory, ah
Today, I still can’t reach you
Though you’re so close
Brought to you by [KawaSubs]